<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>json on An old coder</title>
    <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/json/</link>
    <description>Recent content in json on An old coder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:33:51 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/json/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Testing an App</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/testing-an-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:33:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/testing-an-app/</guid>
      <description>What a crazy few days it has been. I have caught yet another cold which is a reminder of just how much a toxic germ factory a middle-school is as well as an example of why schools are such a horrible vector for covid infections.
I haven&amp;rsquo;t done a lot in the last few days but on Friday I did post a test version of a web application that I have been working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shut it down!</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shut_it_down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shut_it_down/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to say Shut it down! and move on.
I spent the better part of the week working on creating a browser for the modding commands for Conquest of Elysium 5. I had the data for the commands built into a nested JSON file. I built a template for JSRender that took the data and created a collapsible tree menu that let you browse the command structure and then view individual commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Structuring JSON data</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/structuring-json-data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 12:26:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/structuring-json-data/</guid>
      <description>My new project has a lot of text data that is available in a .csv and spreadsheet files but not in any more useful format. I took the .csv data I had an created a sqllite .db file so I could use it to generate some queries to create a .json file which I will use to display the data but also to create the menu system.
The original data is the modding documentation for a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell Scripting</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shell-scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 11:49:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shell-scripting/</guid>
      <description>So I didn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get other work done and went ahead and built the shell script to automate converting all of my csv files. I did a few stackoverflow searches to find some information about getting filenames into a shell script and then iterating over them. I also had to look up how to determine the filename without the extension as I had to create a new .json filename for the output file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More csv work</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/more-csv-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:12:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/more-csv-work/</guid>
      <description>I finally managed to finish my csv to JSON workflow. I originally tried usingMiller to export my csv to JSON but it didn&amp;rsquo;t provide all of the options that I needed. I managed to find a node library called csvtojson that had all of the tools I needed. It also lets you edit the header names to create nested JSON data in a way that I needed as well. I will be keeping Miller handy though as I will have more csv work to do in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Node to build CLI tools</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/usingnode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:46:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/usingnode/</guid>
      <description>So I have been working with various command line tools and apps to try to build a workflow to let me take csv data that I export from a spreadsheet and turn it into JSON. This actually isn&amp;rsquo;t too difficult and there are a lot of tools, like Miller, that will let you take csv and monkey with it. It has a lot of options but many of them seem to be tools to work with CSV, or similar, data and not a lot of them seem to be options for JSON.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using JSON</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/using-json/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 10:12:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/using-json/</guid>
      <description>The problem of serializing data and then importing it back into your application is very, very old. I remember Andy White and a few others discussing approaches to this in Director twenty years ago. Andy came up with some code that could do it in Lingo and then XML became a thing1 and we all started using XML for serializing data. Andy, being Andy, came out with a better, and faster, XML parser than Macromedia did.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
