<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>node on An old coder</title>
    <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/node/</link>
    <description>Recent content in node on An old coder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 09:49:51 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/node/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Have I Learned - Update 2</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/what-have-i-learned-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2021 09:49:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/what-have-i-learned-update-2/</guid>
      <description>Well it has been a busy week. Lets have a look back at all of the new things I have &amp;lsquo;learned&amp;rsquo;1 in order to get my web application up and running.
JSRender and JSView So the biggest thing for me was learning to integrate JSRender and JSView into my web application. I can&amp;rsquo;t get over how well they work and also how easy they were to use. I am not really stressing either library but I took the HTML creation for a fairly complex display and turned it into a template and took the code needed to create it into one line.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shell Scripting</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shell-scripting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 11:49:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shell-scripting/</guid>
      <description>So I didn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get other work done and went ahead and built the shell script to automate converting all of my csv files. I did a few stackoverflow searches to find some information about getting filenames into a shell script and then iterating over them. I also had to look up how to determine the filename without the extension as I had to create a new .json filename for the output file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More csv work</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/more-csv-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 09:12:43 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/more-csv-work/</guid>
      <description>I finally managed to finish my csv to JSON workflow. I originally tried usingMiller to export my csv to JSON but it didn&amp;rsquo;t provide all of the options that I needed. I managed to find a node library called csvtojson that had all of the tools I needed. It also lets you edit the header names to create nested JSON data in a way that I needed as well. I will be keeping Miller handy though as I will have more csv work to do in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Node to build CLI tools</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/usingnode/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 15:46:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/usingnode/</guid>
      <description>So I have been working with various command line tools and apps to try to build a workflow to let me take csv data that I export from a spreadsheet and turn it into JSON. This actually isn&amp;rsquo;t too difficult and there are a lot of tools, like Miller, that will let you take csv and monkey with it. It has a lot of options but many of them seem to be tools to work with CSV, or similar, data and not a lot of them seem to be options for JSON.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
