<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jquery on An old coder</title>
    <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/jquery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in jquery on An old coder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:33:51 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/tags/jquery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Testing an App</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/testing-an-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:33:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/testing-an-app/</guid>
      <description>What a crazy few days it has been. I have caught yet another cold which is a reminder of just how much a toxic germ factory a middle-school is as well as an example of why schools are such a horrible vector for covid infections.
I haven&amp;rsquo;t done a lot in the last few days but on Friday I did post a test version of a web application that I have been working on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shut it down!</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shut_it_down/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 09:05:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/shut_it_down/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes you just have to say Shut it down! and move on.
I spent the better part of the week working on creating a browser for the modding commands for Conquest of Elysium 5. I had the data for the commands built into a nested JSON file. I built a template for JSRender that took the data and created a collapsible tree menu that let you browse the command structure and then view individual commands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Speed of Javascript</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/the-speed-of-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 11:45:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/the-speed-of-javascript/</guid>
      <description>I still have difficulty comprehending the speed at which Javascript runs in the browser. Part of the speed is due to the processors that our computers are running. A more significant amount of the improvement though is the capabilities of the Javascript engines that are being used in browsers as well as the advent of JIT in those engines.
It has dramatically changed not only what you can do in a web-based application but how you do it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
