<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>An old coder</title>
    <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on An old coder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 15:29:15 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Deploying</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/deploying/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 15:29:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/deploying/</guid>
      <description>So it works locally. Now how do we get it to Github?
My first problem is that the repository is private. I need to make it public so that Github Pages will allow me to host it using the free plan that I am using.
Hugo defaults to building all of your static content into the /public directory and Github pages, which assumes that you are using Jekyll wants to find everything in the /doc directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Going</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/getting-going/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 13:12:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/getting-going/</guid>
      <description>You have to assume that any blog that involves using a command line tool and pushing content to a code control system will have a few hickups involved with getting it going. Such is the case with this blog. The Hugo docs seem to be based on the assumption taht you are going to get Github to render the static html pages. So their explanation of the process involves creating a Github Workflow Action.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 11:26:09 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolbat.github.io/zacblog/post/first-post/</guid>
      <description>A new blog A new start as a developer requires, I think, a new blog. And since my focus is going to be Javascript web application development then it seems as if my new blog should not only document that path but also help me along on that path. To that end, I am using the Hugo site generator and Github Pages to create this blog and host it.
There are so many new tools and practices that I am learning that it is all a buzz but it is also quite exciting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
